{
    "subject": "resource/Tau_(sculpture)",
    "predicate": "property/artist",
    "object": "resource/Tony_Smith_(sculptor)",
    "human_readable": "The artist of the sculpture Tau is Tony Smith.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8738171458244324,
            "question": "Is Tony Smith known for creating sculptures?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8459267616271973,
            "question": "How does the sculpture Tau reflect Tony Smith's artistic vision?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8421194553375244,
            "question": "What is the name of the sculpture created by Tony Smith?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8188848495483398,
            "question": "Who created the sculpture Tau?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7002812623977661,
            "question": "What style of art is the sculpture Tau considered to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6129827499389648,
            "question": "Can you name another artwork by Tony Smith?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5080618858337402,
            "question": "What is the significance of the title 'Tau' for the sculpture?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49240177869796753,
            "question": "What makes the sculpture Tau unique or notable?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46273908019065857,
            "question": "Where might the sculpture Tau be displayed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4570883512496948,
            "question": "What artistic medium did Tony Smith work with?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The artist of the sculpture Tau is Tony Smith.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1393_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where might the sculpture Tau be displayed?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1393_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What makes the sculpture Tau unique or notable?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1393_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the significance of the title 'Tau' for the sculpture?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1393_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1393_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1393_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1393_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1393_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1393_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1393_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1393_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1393_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1393_89.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1393_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that confirms Tony Smith created the sculpture TAU. For example, one document states, \"On Wednesday, the Village of South Orange begins installing TAU, an abstract bronze sculpture by famed South Orange native Tony Smith,\" and another mentions, \"Architect, painter, and sculptor Tony Smith (1912 \u2013 80) worked under Frank Lloyd Wright, designed a church with his friend Jackson Pollock, and created monumental abstract sculptures that revolutionized public art as we know it.\" These statements support the triple that Tony Smith is the artist of the sculpture Tau."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}